article.com 2019-06-23

# Privacy Policy - Article - Article | Modern, Mid-Century and Scandinavian Furniture

### Current Version: Ver. 1.0 (15th September 2012)

article.com understands and respects everyone’s privacy rights and will make use of all information collected in a responsible and reasonable manner. Your use of article.com is governed by this Privacy Policy, as updated from time to time. 

### Information

With your use of article.com, we may collect a variety of information from and about you through different means. By way of example, and not limiting the generality of the foregoing, we may collect, store and process your IP address or addresses from which article.com is accessed and also your browser, operating system, platform and location, for, amongst other purposes, to track usage of our site. Also any information posted by you anywhere on article.com may also be collected and use for the aforementioned or other purposes. 

### Use of Cookies

If you use article.com you agree to the use by article.com of cookies, which are small data files sent to your browser for storage on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to identify you, track activity at our site and improve the services therein. 

### Use of Information

You agree that article.com has the right to aggregate personal information about you with that of others who use article.com. We may use such data for, amongst other things, to prepare collective profiles of our users and their activities. For example, we may track the number of our users who request certain search terms or queries or compile data about search queries as they relate to a specific geographic region or a particular good or service. article.com may additionally be required or it may in good faith reasonably believe that it is required to make disclosure of information by law. 

### Sharing of Information

article.com may share your information with third parties such as third party service providers, affiliated businesses, business units and other companies in order for it to conduct its business. For example article.com may share your information for fulfilling orders, managing customer lists, analyzing data and marketing services. article.com may also share your information when it would be appropriate to comply by law. 

### Amendments to Privacy Policy.

As article.com evolves and/or due to changes in business operations, law, regulatory framework and/or for any other reasons appropriate in the reasonable opinion of article.com, this Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. article.com therefore reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time. The revised and most up to date version of the Privacy Policy shall be available at article.com with the date of the current version indicated at the head of the document. The applicable Privacy Policy shall always be the most current version.
